I ask Ukrainians one specific one
я задаю украинцам один конкретный один
specific question Why in
конкретный вопрос Почему на территории
Ukraine until 2014 they did not introduce
Украины до 2014 года не ввели вторым
Russian as a second state language as they
государственным русский язык как это
did, for example, in Belarus And in
сделали допустим в Белоруссии И в
principle there are many such states I explain I explain
принципе таких государств много Объясняю
Yes, look Yes, this is the policy of the
Объясняю Да смотри Да это политика
Anglo-Saxons to divide our fraternal
англосаксов по разделению наших братских
peoples They did, mind you, in Ukraine
народов Они сделали ты заметь в Украине
they did not, on principle, introduce Russian as a
не они принципиально не вводили русский
second state language And in Russia,
язык вторым государственным И в России в
where 5 million Ukrainians live,
которой живёт 5 млн украинцев
on principle, they did not introduce
принципиально не вели вторым
Ukrainian as a second state language
государственным украинский язык
Hello,
Здравствуйте
Great We seemed to be talking somehow with you Where are you from From Chelyabinsk
Здорово Общались вроде как-то с тобой
from the Southern Urals
Откуда С Челябинска с Южного Урала Ты
Where are you from My father is from Chelyabinsk And
откуда У меня родом отец с Челябинска А
now I am from Kyiv It
я сейчас из Киева
happens About what in general What do you talk about
Бывает О чём вообще Чем беседуешь
in unison What will have to be What do you
в унисон О чём придётся
think why Russia is fighting with
Как считаете зачем Россия воюет с
Ukraine
Украиной
Destroy
Уничтожить
Nazi ideology in general Nazi ideology
нацистскую вообще нацистскую идеологию
must be exterminated root and branch
надо истребить вот под корень
Denazification delization Yeah Let me explain
Денацификация делизация Угу Вот поясню
right away We consider Ukrainians to be one
сразу Мы считаем украинцев ну одним
people with us Here Ukrainians are
народом с нами Вот украинцы - это
Russians Belarusians are one people In
русские белорусы - это один народ По
essence, it’s like it’s not  there was such a
сути его как бы и не было такого такой
nationality Ukrainians before the beginning of the
национальности украинцы до начала грубо
20th century, roughly speaking It was invented It's a
говоря XX века Она была придумана Это
nationality yes Here And you think we are
национальность да Вот А у вас считают мы
sincere Ukrainians Ukraine is independent you are
щиры украинцы Украина незалежна вы
Russians
русские
No Eh, have
Нет Ээ
you ever heard what they were
у нас вот ты слышал когда-нибудь что в
shouting in Moscow
Москве орали
there something like that For us,
там ну что-нибудь такое Для нас
Ukrainians are one people with us And you
украинцы один народ с нами А у вас
made a division such a
именно сделали разделение такое
specific division We are sincere Ukrainians And
конкретное разделение Мы щиры украинцы А
you made
вы сделал
your Yeltsin Look, we were one people We
ваш Ельцин Смотри мы один народ были Мы
all lived in the Russian Empire Your Lenin
в Российской империи все жили Ваш Ленин
took the Russian Empire and
взял развалил Российскую империю и
shot the Tsar
расстрелял царя
Notice And why a small small
Заметьте И почему маленький маленький
nuance And why And why our Lenin And
нюанс А почему А почему наш Ленин А
why not our common Lenin Well, the fact that
почему не наш общий Ленин Ну то что он
he lived
то что он жил
there in Switzerland there in England there in
там в Швейцарии там в Англии там в
Sweden Why Why do you erect monuments to him
Швеции Почему Почему вы памятники ему
then We all think that
тогда ставите Мы все мы считаем что
Lenin And why
Ленин А зачем вот этой вот ерундой
engage in this nonsense Well, this scarecrow stands and stands
заниматься Ну стоит это чучело и стоит
He took the Russian Empire and
Он взял развалил Российскую империю он
invented Belarus Kazakhstan Ukraine We
попридумал Беларусь Казахстан Украину Мы
said: "No, we don't remember life since the
сказали: "Нет мы по помним жизнь со
times of Rus' in a single  state" Yes And
времён Руси в едином государстве" Да И
Lenin, specifically on orders from these
Ленин специально по заказам вот этих
German special services, took and divided the
немецких спецслужб взял разделил
Russian Empire, invented Ukraine, invented
Российскую империю придумал Украину
Belarus, invented Kazakhstan There were no
придумал Беларусь придумал Казахстан Не
such countries He invented the RSFSR Well, it's
было ж таких стран Придумал РСФСР Ну аж
funny, yes Russian Soviet
смешно да Российская Советская
Federative Socialist Republic
Федеративная Социалистическая Республика
Five letters in the abbreviation You can't even
Пять букв в аббревиатуре Аж не
pronounce it And he
выговоришь Да и напридумал он в России
invented all these republics in Russia Chechnya
попридумал республики все эти Чечня там
used to be the Cossack army and everything And
раньше как было казачье войско и всё А
now Dagestan is not there, well, there was a
сейчас Дагестан там не ну там было
division I'm with you, I'm with you, sorry, I'll
деление Я с тобой я с тобой извини
interrupt, I partly agree because there was a
перебью отчасти соглашусь потому что и
province, district, region, division, there was such a thing So
было губерния уезд область деление было
look, yes, the thing is that,
такое Так вот смотри да дело в том что
uh, the Anglo-Saxons, you know, against us Slavs, the Anglo-Saxons have
ээ англосаксы ты же знаешь против нас
always been against us Slavs - they were the
славян всегда англосаксы - это были
main opponents of the Slavs Uh, who
самые главные противники славян Ээ кто
destroyed the Russian Empire, it turns out,
развалил Российскую империю получается
agent Lenin, yes, with the money of the
агент Ленин да на деньги
Anglo-Saxons, the money of world capitalism,
англосаксов деньги мирового капитализма
yes, that's what they did, they immediately
да вот что сделали они сразу же
divided it so that under Lenin
разделили чтобы мы и при Ленине началась
this Ukrainization would begin Let's embroidered shirts, let's come up with
вот эта украинизация Давайте вышиваночки
all this for you Belarusians
давайте вам это всё белорусов придумать
Belarusians  never existed at all, you
Белорусов вообще никогда ну не
know They were invented by
существовало понимаешь Их придумали
Belarusians Well, why were there Little Russians,
белору Ну почему были малоросые
White Russians, Great Russians and so on Well, yes,
белороссые великороссые и так далее Ну
but there were no Belarusians Yes, that was all
да но белорусов не было да Это всё было
And this one took, uh, Lenin and invented the
А этот взял ээ Ленин и придумал
Belarusian Soviet Socialist
Белорусскую Советскую Социалистическую
Republic With him, at first, in with the
Республику С он вообще сначала в со
capital in Smolensk, and then he
столицей в Смоленске сделал а потом уже
realized that it would be better to take Smolensk into the republic And so
понял что лучше Смоленск в ресфр забрать
Lenin, when Stalin died,
Вот И Ленин когда помер Сталин то
mixed this thing up a little because
немножко перемешал эту штуку потому что
he realized, well, that Lenin had messed up a little with
он понял ну что Ленин немножко намутил с
these divisions, yes, but Stalin
этими разделениями да но Сталин уже
somehow did not dare to unite everything so that there would be
как-то не решился объединить всё чтобы
no republics, so that there would be one
не было республик чтобы была одна
republic He did not live to see the war, Hitler
республика Не дожил он война ему Гитлер
prevented him from doing that Yes, in
помешал вот это сделать Да Вот в
fifty-three, when Stalin or in
пятьдесят третьем когда Сталин или в
fifty-sixth, in what year was he there, when he
пятьдесят шестом в каком он там когда
died in fifty-three on March 5,
уже в пятьдесят третьем умер 5 марта
fifty-three, yes, when he
пятьдесят третьего года да когда он
kicked the bucket, yes, this
двинул дуба да пришёл вот этот
Khrushchev came By the way, Khrushchev was from Ukraine,
Хрущёв Это кстати Хрущёв был с Украины
if anything A small, very
если что Маленькая такая очень
specific remark No, he is not from Ukraine, he is
конкретная ремарка Не он не с Украины он
from, to be more precise, from the Kursk region From the
с если точнее с Курской области С
Kursk region Well  one way or another he was he was
Курской области Ну так или иначе он был
constantly in charge of Ukraine He was in charge so much
он управлял постоянно Украиной Управлял
that his hands were covered in
так что у него руки по локти были в
blood up to his elbows Even Stalin yelled at him: "What are you
крови Даже даже Сталин ему орал: "Ты что
doing there, fool? Calm down He
там дурень делаешь Уймись Он там полу
shot half of Ukraine there It was brutal, yes,
Украины поперестрелял Так это жесть был
brutal With Khrushchev, look" And then, yes,
да Жесть С Хрущёвый смотри" И дальше да
then in 1991,
Э потом в девяносто первом
two Yeltsin and Gorbachev took and destroyed the
два Ельцин и Горбачёв взяли развалили на
Soviet Union with American money Listen,
деньги американцев Советский Союз Слушай
also a small
тоже маленькая
remark Gorbachev was not he was
ремарочка Горбачёв не был он был
corrupt These are the three three who
продажный были Это три три которые в
smashed it in Belovezhskaya Pushcha Kravchuk Yeltsin
беловежской пуще забхали Кравчук Ельцин
and Shushkevich Shushkevich Yes And look, it
и Шушкевич Шушкевич Да И смотри
turns out Kravchuk Yeltsin and Shushkevich yes
получается Кравчук Ельцин и Шушкевич да
And look, all this was done with
И смотри это ж всё делалось с ведома
Gorbachev's knowledge because if he had said
Горбачёва потому что если бы он сказал
his no, if he had brought in special forces, nothing
своё нет если бы он завёл спецназ ничего
would have happened, you understand Nothing would have happened
бы не было понимаешь Ничего бы не было
It was, yes The Anglo-Saxons are very cunning They
Это было да Англосакцы очень хитро Они
could not defeat our Soviet state By
не могли победить нашу советскую державу
the way, I was
Я кстати я восемьдесят первого года
born in 1981 What are you
рождения Ты какого
sixty-ninth You are 12 years
шестьдесят девятого Ты на 12 лет меня
younger than me Yes, yes, you are older You, Gagarin
младши Да да ты постарше Ты вот Гагарин
flew into space and was born 8 years later Well,
полетел в космос и через 8 лет и родился
this is generally commendable
Ну это вообще похвально Так
So the Anglo-Saxons could never They were
вот англосаксы никогда не могли Они
afraid of the USSR 1/6 of the land Yes From
боялись СССР 1/6 часть суши Да От
Berlin to Vladivostok there were troops From
Берлина до Владивостока стояли войска От
Berlin to Vladivostok Look, this is
Берлина до Владивостока Посмотри это
almost the entire visible map They were afraid
чуть ли не вся видимая карта Они боялись
They understood that if there was political
Они понимали что если будет политическая
will and tank wedges would cross into the English
воля да танковые клиния перейдут в
Channel They understood this And that's all And this entire
Ламанш Они это понимали И всё И вся эта
Anglo-Saxon, let's
англо-саксонская
say, British civilization that
ээ скажем цивилизация британская которая
robbed colonies all its life and
грабила ээ колонии всю свою жизнь и на
parasitized on this would be destroyed
этом паразитировала она бы уничтожилась
And they were afraid of this They did everything to
И они это боялись Они делали всё чтобы
destroy our Soviet homeland Our
развалить нашу советскую родину Нашу
Soviet homeland They let this
советскую родину Они тут пускали этот
voice of America out here and so on Yes, I know
голос Америки и так дальше Да я знаю
Because here in Ukraine we have
Потому что у нас вот тут в Украине есть
people who listened to the radio and specially
люди они слушали радио да специально им
transmitted frequencies from Europe to them
транслировали из Европы доходили сюда
and they listened they didn't listen to
частоты да и они слушали они не слушали
our Soviet television so  they
наше советское телевидение так они
thought that we were being deceived here and that they
считали что нас тут обманывают и что
had achieved Who is who who are they Well, those
добились Кто кто кто они Ну вот эти
who wanted to listen to Europe and America,
которые хотели слушать Европу и Америку
you know, the voice of America, all sorts of
понимаешь голос Америки слушали всякие
people listened to it here And that's what happened In
люди тут Вот И что получилось В
1991, when Yeltsin and
девяносто первом году когда Ельцин с
Gorbachev were destroying the Soviet Union,
Горбачёвым разваливает Советский Союз
what were the Americans doing? Gorbachev took in
американцы что делают Горбачёв взял в
1989, withdrew troops from
восемьдесят девятом вывел войска из
East Germany and destroyed the Berlin
Восточной Германии и развалил берлинскую
Wall The Americans immediately NATO put
стену Американцы сразу НАТО оп запустила
its roots there Gorbachev withdrew troops from
туда свои корни Горбачёв вывел войска из
Poland from the Warsaw Pact countries Poland
Польши из стран Варшавского блока Польша
Czechoslovakia Hungary What happened right away
Чехословакия Венгрия Что сразу случилось
Chukh, NATO entered there Yes, Czechoslovakia was
Чух туда вошло НАТО Да Чехословакию
dismembered into the Czech Republic Slovakia too, so that Yugoslavia was taken in Well,
расчленили на Чехию Словакию тоже чтобы
that's their business,
было Югославию взяли в Ну это их дела
it doesn't concern us at all Yes, yes, but
это вообще нас не касается Да да но
Yugoslavia, yes, Yugoslavia was surrounded
Югославию да Югославию взяли в кольцо
Under the Soviet Union, no one would have
При Советском Союзе никто бы Югославию
bombed Yugoslavia No one And so Yugoslavia, where is Yugoslavia
бомбил Никто бы А так Югославия где
now They destroyed the Soviet
сейчас Югославия Они развалили Советский
Union and they destroyed Yugoslavia
Союз и они развалили Югославию
specifically into many small republics
специально на много маленьких республик
And we all lived with the Soviet Union 15
И с Советским Союзом мы все жили 15
Slavic  republics Ukrainians there
славянских республик украинцы там
Lithuanians Kazakhs Russians we were all
литовцы казахи русские мы все были
one people We are all damn I don't know since
единый народ Мы все блин я не знаю со
the time of Rurik we fought in these territories
времён Рюрика мы ж на этих территориях
against the Anglo-Saxons And it
как бы против англосаксов воевали И
turns out that now in
получается что теперь они в девяносто
1991 as soon as Yeltsin and
первом году сразу же как только Ельцин с
Gorbachev said that the Soviet Union would
Горбачёвым сказали что Советский Союз
fall apart they the Americans came here to
развалится они зашли американцы сюда в
Ukraine Do you think we have serious
Украину Ты думаешь у нас тут серьёзно
elections here They appoint a president for us
выборы есть Они нам ставят президента
which one they need to show They hold elections as if
какого им нужно показать Проводят вроде
They came to Belarus in Latvia
как выборы Они зашли в Беларусь в Латвию
Lithuania in Estonia And you remember under
Литву в Эстонию И у вас ты помнишь при
Yeltsin in your White House the whole sixth
Ельцине в Белом доме вашем весь шестой
floor of American advisers sat They
этаж советников американских сидел Они
wrote the constitution for you Well I
же конституцию вам писали Ну я этих
don't know these details but I fully
подробностей не знаю но вполне себе
admit it Here And here is yours which is the
допускаю Вот И вот ваша эта которая
Central Bank Elvira
Центробанк Эльвира
Nabiullina why can't they do it in any way she is
Набиулина почему её не могут никак она
already raising the key rate How much did she
уже поднимает ключевую ставку Сколько 22
raise 22 or 23
или 23 подняла Ты вот вот это вот
You are a little bit of an adult what are
немножко ты вот взрослый человек ты что
you saying Nabiullina there is like ours our most
ты говоришь набиулино там как у нас наш
serene  will say so and it will be What
светлейший скажет так оно и будет Что
Nabiullina Is it something she decides or something
набиулина Это что-то она решает что ли
No So the question is why won't they
Нет Так вопрос поче почему её не
change her That is, uh And why So it
поменяют То есть ээ А а зачем Значит
suits our government So the
устраивает правительство наше Так вот
thing is that look the thing is that you
дело в том что смотри дело в том что ты
understand that both Yeltsin and Putin are
же понимаешь что и Ельцин и Путин - это
just talking dolls Behind them are those
просто говорящие куклы За ними стоят те
who really govern
кто действительно управляют
Russia Behind Yeltsin And now from this
Россией За Ельцином А вот теперь с этого
point in more detail Well, up to this
места поподробнее Вот э вот до вот этого
point you basically shocked me with
момента ты меня в принципе шокировал
your tirade with which I agree 99%
своей тирадой с которой я на 99%
Here about who
согласен Вот насчёт того что кто кем
governs whom and what is happening Look,
управляет и что происходит Вот смотри
from the moment when
вот с момента с момента когда произошло
the division took place, roughly speaking, why Belarus,
разделение грубо говоря почему Беларусь
roughly speaking, ended up on Russia's side
грубо говоря оказалась на стороне России
Well, we are, as it were, a union state
Ну и мы как бы союзное государство
today there are no questions in the
сегодня никаких вопросов нет в
customs union Kazakhs are also,
таможенном союзе Казахи как бы
more or less, a union state, a
более-менее тоже союзное государство
customs union and so on Why did
таможенный союз и так далее Почему
Ukraine take such an aggressive
Украина заняла такую агрессивную
policy towards Russia Okay, there
политику в отношении России Ладно там
NATO NATO is policy The
НАТО НАТО - это политика
European Union is policy You are
Евросоюз это политика Ты правильный
asking the right question Look, I'll tell you why
вопрос задаёшь Смотри я скажу почему Вот
I'm just, well, sorry, you said I can also
я просто ну извини ты говорил тоже могу
ask a question I am asking  Ukrainians one
вопрос задать Я задаю украинцам один
specific one specific question Why
конкретный один конкретный вопрос Почему
in Ukraine until 2014 they did not
на территории Украины до 2014 года не
introduce Russian as the second state
ввели вторым государственным русский
language as they did, for example, in
язык как это сделали допустим в
Belarus And in principle there are many such states I explain I explain
Белоруссии И в принципе таких государств
Yes look Yes this is the
много Объясняю объясняю Да смотри Да это
policy of the Anglo-Saxons to divide our
политика англосаксов по разделению наших
fraternal peoples They did you notice in
братских народов Они сделали ты заметь в
Ukraine they did not make
Украине не они принципиально не вводили
Russian the second state language on principle And in
русский язык вторым государственным И в
Russia, where 5 million Ukrainians live, they did
России в которой живёт 5 млн украинцев
not make
принципиально не вели вторым
Ukrainian the second state language on principle That is,
государственным украинский язык То есть
they with This is not even discussed
они с Это вообще даже не обсуждается
even from our side This analogy this
даже с нашей стороны Это аналогию эту
analogy can be
аналогию можно
drawn
провести
Why in Sweden they did not make Finnish the second
Почему в Швеции не вели вторым финский
This question did not arise at all In Finland they
Этот вопрос вообще не стоял В Финляндии
made the second second Swedish and the
вели вторый второй шведский а
state language And Sweden did not make it the second
государственным А Швеции не вели второй
because it was not in demand Look so look The
потому что им не востребовал Смотри так
fact is that in the Soviet
вот смотри Дело в том что в Советском
Union in the Soviet Union you could
Союзе в Советском Союзе можно было
speak any language: Ukrainian
говорить на любом языке: украинский
Russian and so on
русский и так дальше
yes The Anglo-Saxons specifically did it so that
да Англосаксы специально сделали так
in Ukraine they did not use Russian
чтобы в Украине не использовали русский
and in Russia they did not use Ukrainian They
а в России не использовали украинский
closed the Ukrainian schools that were
Закрыли украинские школы которые были
This is a fact They did it so that we would not
Это факт Они для того чтобы мы вообще не
understand each other at all what we were saying only
понимали друг что мы говорили только
in Ukrainian and you only in Russian Po and
по-украински а вы только по-русски По а
Lithuanians only in Lithuanians Cossacks only
литовцы только по-литовцы казаки только
in Kazakh and so that we do
по-казахски да и чтобы мы вот это
not know these fraternal languages ​​And I will tell you
братские языки мы не знали А я скажу
why Because you know that
почему Потому что ты знаешь что сейчас
global warming is happening now
идёт глобальное потепление
Here Uh and what does global
Вот Ээ а причём здесь глобальное
warming have to do with it And I and I will say look at the
потепление А я а я скажу смотри у
Anglo-Saxons yes all the cities are the most
англосаксов да все города самые
densely populated because they developed a
густонаселённые потому что они развивали
maritime civilization they are located on the
морскую цивилизацию они находятся на
sea coast In 20 years with the
побережье морском Через 20 лет при
warming that is happening now yes
потеплении таком как идёт сейчас да
scientists predict that the level of the world
учёные прогнозируют что уровень мирового
ocean will rise by 1-2 m it can
океана поднимется на 1-2 м может
rise due to the intensity of the melting of
подняться из-за интенсивности тайния
glaciers As a result all these New York
ледников В результате все эти Нью-Йорк
London all these San Francisco and so
Лондон всякие эти Сан-Франциски и так
on yes they will end up and their Venices
дальше да они окажутся и венеции ихние
they will end up flooded and there will be such
они окажутся затоплены да и будут
large-large such human
большие-большие такие человеческие
movements And our territory look at the
перемещения А наша территория посмотри
territory of the Slavic lands yes
территория славянских земель да вот
above the Black Sea it was not flooded
выше Чёрного моря она не затапливалась
yes geologically it was not flooded
да геологически она не затапливалась
the last  50,000 years
последние 50.000 лет
never Geologists and this is fertile land
никогда Геологи и это плодородная земля
That is, a huge number of people can live and feed themselves here
То есть тут может прожить и прокормиться
And there is such a
огромное количество людей И есть такой
project New Khazaria They want to
проект Новая Хазария Они хотят да
clear
очистить от
the territory of the Slavic lands
славян территорию славянских земель
from the Dnieper to the
от Днепра до до
Don from the Slavs and then settle there, if
Дона и заселить туда потом в случае
necessary, their Anglo-Saxon
надобности своих англосаксонских
fellow tribesmen in order to wait out a
соплеменников для того чтобы переждать
new flood They have such a
новый вот такой потоп Есть у них такая
concept And uh, maybe you heard the concept of the
концепция И э может ты слышал концепция
golden billion too, yes, that the population of the
золотого миллиарда тоже да что население
planet is overpopulated and it must be
планеты перенаселено и его надо
reduced by reducing the Slavs
уменьшить за счёт уменьшения славян
because the Slavs occupy an
потому что славяне занимают
ecological niche that competes with the
экологическую нишу которая конкурирует с
Anglo-Saxons The Anglo-Saxons look, they
англосаксами Англосаксы смотри они ж вот
have this British peninsula they
у них это британский полуостров они
always did expansion here to the east
всегда экспансию сюда делали на восток
they wanted They always need to need
хотели Они всегда вот им нужно нужно
because well, to the West, too, roughly speaking,
потому что ну на Запад тоже грубо говоря
America is well this was already colonization
Америка это же ну это уже колонизация
then like yes and there were some
была потом типа да а там какие-то
Indians and here they all wanted resources
индейцы а вот тут они всё хотели ресурсы
resources you understand yes Hitler here
ресурсы понимаешь да Гитлер сюда
Napoleon here like came yes everyone came here you
Наполеон сюда типа шёл да все сюда шли
understand They all came and everyone wanted this
понимаешь Они все шли и все хотели этой
lands like because there are lands up to
землицы типа потому что тут земли до
Sakhalin here And unfortunately I will say
Сахалина есть Вот И к сожалению я скажу
such a problem yes what uh well you think
такую проблемку да что ээ ну ты считаешь
that Putin is still independent No
что Путин всё-таки самостоятельный Нет
Putin he is a puppet who is controlled and he is
Путин он кукла которым управляют и его
used in order to make uh a
используют для того чтобы сделать ээ
war of Slavs against Slavs We are
войну славян против славян У нас же мы
one people - this is a civil war
один народ - это гражданская война
Look how interesting it turns out Yes
Смотри как интересно получается Да
Slavs from Russia and Slavs from
умирают славяне из России и славяне из
Ukraine are dying And for some reason Ramzan Kadyrov, not a
Украины А почему-то Рамзан Кадыров не
Slav, is arming himself to the fullest Did you see
славянин вооружается на полную Ты видел
what is happening with the Akhmat regiment They are all
что там с полком Ахмат делается Они все
like that in short with these with weapons There are 8,000 of them there in
такие короче с этими с оружием Их там в
Chechnya he shows a video
Чечне он там ээ показывает видео стоит
there are 8,000 fighters in Chechnya What are they doing
там 8.000 бойцов в Чечне Что они делают
True Why are they sending Slavic
Правда Почему э отправляют славянских
What is 8,000 Is that a lot or what 8,000 And
Что такое 8.000 Это много что ли 8.000 И
look again why Slavic men are
ещё раз смотри почему славянских мужиков
being sent to fight against Slavic
отправляют воевать против славянских
men yes And uh in Chechnya they are building up
мужиков да А ээ в Чечне наращивают
some kind of group So why would I
какую-то группировку Так а почему я
say Because it was
скажу Потому что это
the Anglo-Saxons after the collapse of the Soviet
англосаксы после развала Советского
Union when  they installed Dudayev Dudayev
Союза когда поставили Дудаева Дудаев же
was also a Soviet general He didn't
был тоже советским генералом Он же не
come from anywhere He's like Kadyrov Kadyrov is
взялся ни откуда Он как Кадыров Кадыров
now a Russian general and this Dudayev
сейчас генерал российский а этот Дудаев
was a Soviet general Yes pilots And what did
был советским генералом Да лётчики И что
they do They wanted this project To set the
сделали Они вот этот проект Поджечь
Caucasus on fire yes but then they didn't have enough
Кавказ хотели да но тогда им не хватило
because there weren't enough weapons in the Caucasus There weren't enough
потому что на Кавказе недостаточно было
weapons Now
оружия Недостаточно было оружия Сейчас
through uh Kadyrov the Caucasus has been pumped up Just
через ээ Кадырова Кавказ накачали Просто
look uh under the Soviet Union the Chechens did
посмотри ээ при Советском Союзе чеченцы
n't feel so calm in Moscow
себя так спокойно в Москве не
that he could come there and
чувствовали чтобы он мог там прийти
beat up a Russian for example yes or there now
русского побить например да или там
now no one will tell Kadyrov Yes
сейчас сейчас Кадырову никто не скажет
there are Russians You can say something to
Да есть русских Ты можешь что-то сказать
Kadyrov The truth is you won't say That is and And
Кадырову Правда не скажешь То есть и А
what what to say If a Chechen beats a
что что сказать Если чеченец побьёт
Russian in Moscow at all you won't
русского в Москве вообще ты ничего не
say anything to Kadyrov really In general I mean Well
скажешь Кадырову правда Вообще в смысле
he had a precedent recently
Ну вот у него недавно прецедент был
there uh one Chechen there roughly
произошёл там ээ чеченец один там грубо
speaking made a fuss in Moscow There was
говоря устроил кипиш в Москве Там
some kind of conflict there the security forces
какой-то конфликт произошёл его силовики
accepted him and presented Kadyrov with a charge
приняли и Кадырову предъявили Вот так и
This one is behaving outrageously. He is
так Вот этот себя ведёт безобразно Он
Kadyrov. Let me take him to Grozny. I
Кадыров давайте мне его в Грозный я его
will deal with him. He: "Come to Grozny
с ним разберусь Он: "Приедешь в Грозный
and we will talk." And in short, he
и мы с тобой поговорим" И короче он
left for Grozny and never leaves there
уехал в Грозный и оттуда не вылазиет
again. So, I understand that about the
больше Так что насчёт того что там
Chechens committing lawlessness in
чеченцы беспределит беспределяют в
Moscow.
Москве это
Well, in short, look, I see this
понял Ну короче смотри я я смотрю такую
trend. They are bringing you Tajiks. Well, have you
тенденцию да таджика вам навозят Ну ты
seen how many migrants they brought to Russia?
видел сколько мигрантов навезли в Россию
It's just awful. For example, I am
Просто это ужас просто Я я вот например
also partly a migrant. I myself
тоже от части мигрант Я сам с Казахстана
was born in Kazakhstan and raised in Kazakhstan. I have lived half my life. I
в Казахстане родился вырос Э полжизни
came to Mother Russia in
прожил Приехал в Россию матушку в
Chelyabinsk. And I live normally here.
Челябинск И живу здесь нормально я вижу
And by the way, I welcome my position. This is the
И я кстати моя позиция я приветствую Это
only small nuance. It is
единственное маленький нюанс заключается
necessary to conduct a
в чём Надо вести
competent migration policy in this
грамотную миграционную политику в этом
regard. You are not a Slav, you are Kazakh. I am
плане То ты не славянин ты казах
Russian. I am Russian Orthodox. You are from
Я русский Я русский православный Ты из
Kazakhstan. You are Kazakh.
Казахстана Ты казах
I am Russian Orthodox. I am a former
Я русский православный Я бывший
Kazakh. Don't wait. Do you feel the
казахстанец Не подожди Чувствуешь
difference between nationality,
разницу между между национальность
nationality, Ukrainian or, let's say, a
национальность украинец или допустим
citizen of Ukraine. There is.  difference If
гражданин Украины Есть разница Если
you have Avakov or Akhmetov there,
допустим у вас там Аваков или Ахметов
who are they? Are they Ukrainians or something? Are they
они кто такие Они украинцы что ли Они
Russians? And now it turns out you're from
русским а теперь оказывается ты из
Kazakhstan?
Казахстана
No, I live in Russia. I've been living here for a long time,
Нет я в России живу Я уже давно здесь
30 years. So, you weren't born on
живу 30 лет Так ну ты не родился на
Slavic soil, it turns out, yes. Well, my
славянской земле получается да Ну у меня
parents are from here. My parents are from
родители отсюда У меня родители
central Siberia. And they gave birth to me on virgin soil,
центральной полосы Сибири А родили меня
so to speak. I mean, right on the
на целине так скажем В смысле Прямо на
ground. I've heard that. Yes, on the ground, like
земле Слышал такое Да На земле типа
unplowed virgin soil. You were born right on it. I did
непаханная целина Тебя прямо на ней
n't understand. I mean, Yes. That's right, they
родили Не понял В смысле Да Да Вот
were born on unplowed virgin soil. You
именно на непаханной целине родили Город
know the city of Kustanai. I know the North of Kustanai. Yes. Listen,
Кустаная знаешь такой Север Кустаная
wait. Are you in Kotakh?
знаю Да Слушай так подожди Ты в Котах
Is Akhmetov Ukrainian or a citizen of
Ахметов это украинец или гражданин
Ukraine? Akhmetov Rinat Akhmetov He's a Tatar. That's
Украины Ахметов Ринат Ахметов Он татарин
right. Well done, handsome. And you. Well,
Ну правильно Молодец красава Ну а ты Ну
where does he live? Well,
он он живёт где
he's Ukrainian. So he wasn't born in
Ну ну он украинец Так он не родился в
Ukraine. So
Украине
what? He's a citizen of Ukraine. Rinat
Ну и что Он гражданин Украины Ринат
Akhmetov was born in Uzbekistan.
Ахметов в Узбекистане родился
Well, handsome, handsome. Well, is he a citizen of
Ну красавчик молодец Ну он гражданин
Ukraine or not. But he's not Ukrainian. You're a
Украины или нет Да но он не украинец Вот
citizen of Russia. He's a citizen of Ukraine.
ты гражданин России Он гражданин Украины
But you're not Russian. He's a citizen of Ukraine.
Ну ты же не русский Он гражданин Украины
He's a citizen of Ukraine.  Rinat Akhmetov or
Он гражданин Украины Ринат Ахметов или
not Well done So I am a
нет Вот здорово молодец Так вот я
citizen of the Russian Federation So yes but
гражданин Российской Федерации Так да но
you are not Russian
ты не русский
I am Russian No you are Kazakh
Я русский Нет ты ж казах
damn Well you seem to be such a
блин Ну ты вроде начитанный такой
well-read literate blogger and you have no
грамотный там блогер и у тебя нету
understanding of a citizen of, say, a state
понимания гражданин допустим государства
or nationality Do you have a difference
или национальности У тебя есть разница
between a citizen Let's say I have an
между гражданином Вот допустим у меня
Armenian friend You are Orthodox
друг бы арменин Ты православный
I am an Orthodox Christian Well come on 10
Я православный христианин Вот те а ну 10
commandments tell me Listen
заповедей скажи
let's talk on topic
Слушай давай по теме будем разговаривать
Where are you going You are not Orthodox you are a
Ты куда Ты не православный ты
Muslim You went you went off
мусульманин Ты ты пошёл ты пошёл в
topic already going off topic Stop stop stop
сторону уже от темы уходишь Стоп стоп
Why do you Kazakhs introduce yourself as
стоп Зачем вы казахи представляетесь
Slavs
славянами
Why are you You seem to be an adult normal
Зачем ты Ты вроде взрослый нормальный
adequate person If you are Orthodox
адекватный человек Если ты православни
about the Khori commandments name three commandments for
про Хори заповеди назовите три заповеди
me If you built a normal
мне назови Если ты выстраивал нормальный
and adequate dialogue I really
и адекватный диалог Мне очень
liked the monologue this message of yours
понравилсяй монолог вот этот посыл твой
I absolutely agree with it
Я с ним абсолютно согласен
That you deceived me that you are Russian and you are
Что ты меня обманул что ты русский а ты
Kazakh You don't even know a couple of commandments
казах Ты не знаешь даже пару заповедей
You are not Orthodox Let
Ты не православный
me be, say, a Spaniard What's the
Да пускай я буду допустим испанец Какая
difference I am a citizen of the Russian Federation
разница Я гражданин Российской Федерации
Wait then you are Orthodox
Подожди то ты православный
I am Orthodox So what next Father  our you
Я православный Ну и что дальше Отче наш
know at least
знаешь хотя бы
listen I will read you a prayer here in
слушай я тебе что здесь молитву буду в
the roulette sick or our father who
рулетке читать больную или отче наш иже
art in heaven until Well you know or not well
еси на небеси до Ну ты знаешь или не ну
I will read you a prayer
я тебе буду молитву читать Богородица
Virgin Mary rejoice gracious Mary the Lord is with
дева радуйся благодатная Мария Господь с
you on the Father Our Father say the first
тобой на Отче Отче наш скажи первый
verse Our Father I am looking for adequate people
куплет Отче наша Я ищу адекватных людей
You seemed adequate to me in principle
Ты мне показался в принципе адекватным
Yes consider me whoever you like I am a citizen of the
Да считай меня кем угодно Я гражданин
Russian Federation Consider me whoever you like
Российской Федерации Считай кем угодно
Consider me French or Italian What
Считай французом или итальянцем Какая
difference does it make Migrant You are a migrant you came to
разница Мигран Ты мигрант ты приехал в
Russia yes Here Yes I returned to my
Россию да Вот Да Я и вернулся на свою
historical homeland Let's say in
историческую родину Вот допустим в
Russia a lot of Germans lived I have
России очень жило много немцев У меня
German friends in Kazakhstan
друзья немцы есть в Казахстане
Kazakh Germans They left their
казахстанские немцы Они уехали их
actual homeland was Kazakhstan They were
фактическая родина была Казахстан Они
born in
родились в
Kazakhstan and left for their historical
Казахстане уехали на свою историческую
homeland in Germany Exactly the same
родину в Германию Вот точно такая же
situation happened to me Your last name is
ситуация сложилась со мной Фамилия у
Kazakh historically or in your homeland I
тебя казах историческу или родину
didn't understand Your last name is Kazakh or
Не понял Фамилия у тебя казахская или
Russian Russian what
русская Русская какая
Ivanov Not seriously
Иванов Не серьёзно
Seriously  Swear on your honor as a Russian
Серьёзно Поклянись честью русского
Listen, I'll tell you again I want to have an
Слушай я тебе ещё раз повторяю я хочу
adequate normal dialogue You've
вести адекватный нормальный диалог Ты
led the conversation somewhere off topic What
увёл разговор куда-то в тему Какая
difference does it make What difference does it make what my
разница Какая разница кто я по
nationality is I'll say which one Because I'm either
национальности Я скажу какая раз Потому
Greek yes Because I'm
что я или там грек да Потому что я или
Georgian I'm a Slav, a citizen of the
грузин Я как славяннин гражданин
Russian Federation I, as a Slav,
Российской Федерации Я как славянин с
spoke to you as if you were a Slav, and you turned out to be a
тобой как со славянином говорил а ты
Kazakh or whoever I can't understand
оказался казахом или кем Не могу понять
I'm Russian
Я русский
Swear that you're Russian I swear Everything's
Поклянись что ты русский Клянусь Всё
fine I give you the cross that I'm Russian
хорошо Вот тебе крест даю что я русский
Everything's fine Okay Then you just confused me with
Всё хорошо О'кей Тогда просто ты меня с
this Kazakhstan and I think,
этим Казахстаном что-то спутал и я думаю
damn, I'm crucifying myself now crucifying myself and you, well, you're
блин я сейчас распинаюсь распинаюсь а ты
Germans I have fellow countrymen from Kustanai
ну немцы Вот у меня земляков с Кустаная
who are, well, Germans, ethnic Germans Everything Well,
которые ну немцы этнические немцы Всё Ну
if you swore okay Everything here yes I understood
если ты поклялся о'кей Всё тут да понял
this because they left for their
такое потому что они уехали на
historical homeland in Germany and that's it And they
историческую родину в Германию и всё И
live I'll tell you why I react this way
живут я скажу почему так я реагирую
Because there are a lot of non-Slavs They are
Потому что очень много не славян Они
now pretending to be Slavs that we are brothers,
сейчас косят под славян что мы братья
Slavs there You start talking to them
славяне там Ты начинаешь с ними говорить
he's like: "Oh  and I am a Buryat and I am like a Tatar
он такой: "О а я бурят а я типа татарин
and I am a Tajik You are like: "Damn, well, we have this
а я таджики Ты такий: "Блин ну у нас это
very federal state, this is the thing here,
самое федеративное государство тут дело
it has no fundamental significance I
такое это принципиального значения не
mean, a federation We have a very
имеет В смысле федера У нас очень
multinational state If anything,
многоциональное государство Если что
wait, then you are a federal state - that is, you are
подожди то вы федеративное - это что Вы
federators, it turns
федерасты
out Well, what are the residents of the federation called And in Germany, what are they
называется А а вот в Германии они как
called Citizens of the Federal
называются Граждане Федеративной
Republic of Germany Are
Республики Германии Они федерасты что ли
they federators or something Well, they are federators And you are federators, it
Ну они федерасты И вы федерасты
turns out
получается
I am telling you again, I was
Я тебе ещё раз говорю я
still you, it seems, until this very moment,
ещё ты вроде до вот вот этого момента
when you started this kind of rotten
вот когда ты начал этот какой-то гнилой
bazaar that is incomprehensible to me, you spoke
базар непонятный для меня ты говорил
quite reasonably, competently, normally I
вполне себе разумно грамотно нормально Я
agreed with you 99% Are you now
на 99% был с тобой согласен Ты сейчас
going somewhere into some kind of these wilds Then, by
полез То ты по
nationality, you are a federator, not a federator, you are
национальности федераст не федераст ты
molding something here, I don’t understand Okay,
какую-то лепишь тут я не пойму Ладно всё
then, this one Okay, let's get back to
тогда вот этот Хорошо возвращаемся к
our conversation Then I will believe you that
нашему разговору Тогда я поверю тебе что
you are Russian Orthodox Well  Damn, it's up to
ты русский православный Ну блин ну это
you Believe it or not It's
дело твоё Хочешь верь хочешь не верь Это
not important Well, let's continue this
не принципиально Ну давай продолжим этот
conversation Let's continue What do you think,
наш разговор Продолжим Как ты считаешь
well, why did the Anglo-Saxons manage to do it,
ну почему как англосакцы смогли вот у
in the Soviet Union we had the best
нас в Советском Союзе было самое лучшее
education, the best, yes Well, it's a moot
образование самое лучшее да Ну спорный
point, let's say, one of the very best,
вопрос так скажем одно из самых лучших
Harvard,
самых Гарвард
Princeton, you can't dispute that they are also
Принстон нельзя оспаривать что они тоже
good universities there, yes The question
хорошие там вузы да Вопрос получается
here is how it happened, yes, what did the Anglo-Saxons
тут такой как вышло да что англосакцы
do so that the population of 1/6 of the land became
сделали так что население 1/6 части суши
dumb
тупело
after the collapse of the Soviet Union, just
после развала Советского Союза просто
simple, simple, gullible, naive There is
простые простые доверчивые наивные Вот
such a national Slavic trait,
есть такая национальная славянская черта
gullibility and naivety Well,
доверчивость и наивность Вот Ну обманули
I can say they deceived us like this, they cheated
я могу сказать вот так вот
us, like, let's say, they cheated us, they deceived us, they swindled us You
надули как вот допустим ну надули
can even
обманули объярили Можно то там уже даже
come up with some obscene epithets there, yes The same thing as, I don't
придумать да То же самое как вот я не
know, they got divorced with this revolution,
знаю там вот развели с этой революции
which they staged, they fought, they
которую вот революцию устроили воевали
fought, it seems, here it is, victory for themselves They
воевали уже вроде вот она себе победа
should have already Admiral Kolchak should have been there in the
Должны уже там адмирал Колчак должен был
year yes yes  Admiral Kolk was already supposed to
году да да адмирал Колк уже должен был
land in Constantinople And then
высаживаться в Константинополе И тут
bam the tsar is led by these uh
трах-бах царь ведётся вот на эти ээ
conversations of General Alekseev and with him
разговоры генерала Алексеева и же с ним
that well, it is necessary to abdicate the throne
что ну надо отрекаться от престола как
somehow and so Well, look, they
бы так и так Ну так это ж смотри они
see, I'm telling you, they could never
видишь я же говорю они никогда не могли
defeat Russia by force Yes They
победить Россию силовым путём да Они её
wanted to somehow dismember it from the inside and they
хотели изнутри как-то расчленить и у них
succeeded in this in 1917 through
получилось это в семнадцатом году через
agent Ulyanov Yes in
агента Ульянова да в девяносто первом
1991 through agent Gorbachev and Yeltsin Yes
году через агента Горбачёва и Ельцина да
And now they are promoting this uh
И вот сейчас они продвигают вот этот ээ
narrative again and again I'll tell you more
нарратив снова и снова Я тебе больше
I found a book in Ukraine, they
скажу Я в Украине ээ тут нашёл книгу они
published it, a CIA agent wrote it called
издали црушник написал называется
"The Impossible State" That's in short, how is it
"Неспроможна держава" Это короче как это
in Russian In short, fail state In general, about the
по-русски Короче fail state В общем про
collapse of Russia, Janusz Bugajski, a
развал России Януш Бугайский работник
CIA employee, wrote a whole book in 1922
ЦРУ в двадцать втором году написал целую
"How to Destroy Russia There is about
книгу "Как разваливать Россию там про
republics and everything" Yes And in
республики про всё" Да И в двадцать
1924, in Ukraine, it was published I'm
четвёртом у нас в Украине её выпустили Я
looking at the shelves  wow That is, I
смотрю на полки ничего себе То есть я
took to see that the Anglo-Saxons are
взял посмотреть что это англосаксы
working very hard here in this regard
работают очень сильно тут в этом плане
Very hard They write how to
Очень сильно Они пишут как по
destroy Russia on a religious theme as
религиозной теме разваливать Россию как
on an ethnic one like damn it's terrible They
по этнической как блин там ужас Они
work very hard I see that uh
работают очень сильно Я смотрю что ээ
since they destroyed the Russian Empire in 1917
так как в 1917 развалили Российскую
like they destroyed the
империю как в девяносто первом развалили
Soviet Union in 1991 they now want to
Советский Союз они так хотят сейчас
destroy the Russian Federation and
развалить Российскую Федерацию и
end uh let's say the occupation of these
закончить ээ вот это скажем оккупацию
resources of the great mother Russia you
вот этих ресурсов великой матушки России
know Yes Well that's
понимаешь
happiness I agree with you Well
Да Ну вот счастье я с тобой
roughly speaking during
согласен Ну грубо говоря в течение
one century they
одного века
deceived Russia twice I agree the
обманули Россию два раза Согласен
revolution and 1917 1917
революция и семнадцатый семнадцатый год
and 1991 That's quite
и девяносто первый год Это оно вполне
history goes in a spiral Regarding
себе история идёт по спирали Насчёт того
what you are saying now quite
что ты говоришь сейчас вполне себе
theoretically what you are talking about I
теоретически то что о чём ты говоришь я
partly agree with you such a topic is
с тобой согласен отчасти такая тема
theoretically possible how it will turn out in
теоретически возможно как оно выйдет на
reality here is such a thing War the plan
самом деле тут дело такое Война план
will show Listen you shocked me a little
покажет Слушай ты меня несколько
I saw you several times
шокировал Я тебя несколько раз видел
uh on YouTube Somehow there you have such
ээ в Ютубе Как-то там у тебя такие
slightly different conversations and you  I'll
немножко другие разговоры а ты прямо я
explain it straight I'll explain why Look, the thing is that
объясню Я объясню почему Смотри дело в
I'm on the territory of Ukraine, I'm
том что я нахожусь на территории Украины
not allowed Are you recording me
мне нельзя Ты мне записываешь
No, no, I'm not allowed Well, how about just
Нет не да мне нельзя ж ну как бы
saying what I think You
довольно говорить то что я думаю Ты же
understand that if I say such
понимаешь что если я буду говорить такие
things, they'll knock on my door and say, like they
вещи да ко мне постучат в двери и скажут
just knocked on yours You see Well, there are
там вот как тебе сейчас постучали Видишь
family matters here, yes And they'll lead and
А ну тут семейные дела да А это ведут и
say, look, Andrey, you're saying a little bit of
скажут что смотри Андрей ты немножко
things that you shouldn't
говоришь такие вещи которые не стоит
say, yes, because our ocean
говорить да потому что нашим океанским
partners don't like it Yes,
партнёрам это не нравится да Вот
naturally, I can't talk And when I
естественно я не могу говорить А когда я
understand, I see that I meet a kindred spirit,
понимаю я вижу встречаю родственную душу
I understand that the person most likely isn't
я понимаю что человек скорее всего не
recording Yes, I can have a heart-to-heart talk Yes,
записывает да я могу поговорить по душам
I say, I hope you're
да я говорю надеюсь ты
not recording this and won't post it Such a
это не записываешь и не выложишь такой
change Well, I'm not
меняж ну откровения мои
recording these revelations of mine now, I'm not recording them
эти не не записываю сейчас вот не
and won't post them But here's a cross for you
записываю и не выложу А вот тебе крест
The thing is Well, you shocked me, you shocked me, I did
Дело такое Ну ты меня ты меня ты меня
n't even expect to
шокировал просто Я даже не ожидал вот
hear such a passage, so to speak,
такой вот пассаж услышать так скажем
such a tirade I don't even know what to
тираду такую Прямо не знаю даже что и
say The only question I have for you,
говорить Единственный у меня как бы тебе
as you see, let's say  the
вопрос Как ты видишь вот допустим
end of this conflict
окончание вот этого вот ээ конфликта
that is now terrible hard
который сейчас страшный тяжёлый
bad happening on the territory of
нехороший происходит на территории
Ukraine Your your vision Yes Yes Uh I
Украины Тво твоё видение Да Да Ээ я
see that the Anglo-Saxons have launched such a
смотрю что англосаксы запустили такую
game of good cop and bad
игру в хороший полицейский и плохой
cop Yes 100% agree Yes
полицейский Да 100% согласен Да Вот
They made Trump like a good guy, but
Трампа они сделали как хороший по он
now I will reconcile you, I will reconcile you, and the British are
сейчас я вас помирю помирю а британцы
like chug-chug-chug like we will now
типа чух-чух-чух типа мы сейчас вас
quarrel you That is, and they are playing this
поссорим То есть и они играют вот эту
game they will continue to play now Yes
волыну они будут ещё сейчас играть да
This is all a bait so that the
Это вся затравочка для того чтобы
Slavs relax and think: "Now
славяне расслабились и думали: "Сейчас
Trump will come and restore order" Like
уже Трамп придёт порядок наведёт" Типа
yes Trump doesn't care he is an old man he is
да Трампу всё равно он старый дед он
just a puppet of the Rothschilds and
просто марионетка Ротшильдов и
Rockefellers So he just
Рокфелеров Так он просто одного деда с
replaced one old man with dementia with another old man with
деменцией заменили на другого деда с
dementia You saw there he doesn't remember
деменцией Ты же видел он там не помнт
what he said yesterday That's why yes these are
что он говорил вчера Вот поэтому да это
all games their task is the dismemberment of the
всё это игры у них задача расчленение
Russian Federation This is theirs and
Российской Федерации Вот это ихнее это и
the devastation of the slen That's why here uh I will say
опустошение слен Поэтому тут ээ я скажу
so the Caucasus they  they will set the Caucasus on fire yes
так Кавказ они будут поджигать Кавказ да
definitely through Kadyrov not through
однозначно через Кадырова не через
Kadyrov it will be the Caucasus will flare up Uh
Кадырова оно Кавказ сполыхнёт будет Ээ
they processed the concept of BLM like uh
они обработали концепцию BLM типа ээ
Black Leaves Matters remember like that
Black Leaves Matters помнишь типа что
black lives matter yes when like there uh
жизни чёрных важны да когда типа там ээ
black people spoke out for their rights In
чернокожие выступали за свои права В
Russia this is also being prepared the so-called
России это готовится тоже так называемый
black Maidan through these migrants
чёрный майдан через вот этих мигрантов
yes who are brought in huge
да которых навозят огромными
quantities Yes you saw in your
количествами Да ты же видел у вас на
Uraza Bayram on Uranbairam huge
Ураза Байрам на Уранбайрам огромные
numbers of them take to the streets so
количество они выходят на улицы так
Muslims men not just women but
мусульман мужиков не просто женщин но
us Orthodox you have
нас православные у вас там в церквях
grandmothers and women going to churches and they have
ходят бабушки просто да женщины а у них
men Men who slaughter a ram on the holiday
мужики Мужики которые на праздник режут
They each have a knife you
барана У них у каждого есть нож
understand If they
понимаете Если они по вот так щелчку
take
пальца своих натовских кураторов выйдут
to the streets at the right moment at the snap of a finger of their NATO curators yes it will be
на улицы в нужный момент да там будет
very like tough That's why a
очень типа жёстко Поэтому в России
black Maidan is being prepared in Russia A
готовится чёрный майдан Вот в России
black Maidan is being prepared in Russia And it is not clear
готовится чёрный майдан И непонятно
when they will launch It was also in the Soviet Union
когда они запустят Вот в Советском Союзе
everything seemed to be fine
тоже вроде всё было нормально нормально
then the State Emergency Committee and everything And in 3  the day of the
потом ГКЧП и всё И через 3 дня
Soviet Union is gone And now it will be
Советского Союза не стало И вот будет
exactly the same Nobody will know what they will
точно такая же Никто не будет знать что
do Black Maidan and
что сделают Чёрный майдан и
everything And it will crumble very much They are all there,
всё И посыпется очень Они ж эти все там
uh, Chechens, Tatars, Yakuts, they are sitting and
вот эээ чеченцы татары якуты они сидят и
waiting for when it will be possible, uh, when the
ждут когда можно будет ээ когда ослабнет
federal
федеральный
freeze will weaken M
завис M
And the grandfather lost his temper We didn’t have time to
А сорвался дед Мы ему не успели
tell him that we were
рассказать что мы их
trolling them How easy it is to
троллили Как их легко
reprogram them is just brutal He didn’t
перепрограммировать просто жесть
even buy it when I made fun
Он даже уже не выкупил когда я стебался
of him that he was Kazakh, that he was a fiderast and he
с него что он казах что он фидераст и он
just didn’t do it well, come on And you
прямо не нуто хорошо давай же И ты
start to pile on to him further and he
начинаешь ему дальше наваливать и он
switches back to listening mode Brutal
снова включается в режим слушать Жесть
Like subscribe comment Subscribe to my
Лайк подписка комент Підпишись на мій
Instagram I don’t know why you are here, why are
Instagram Я не знаю для чго це тобі для
you still there looking at my Face,
чого ще тобі там дивитись на мій Face
but for you it’s one, two or three clicks
але для тебе це один два або три клика
But you support me and I will say:
Але ти підтримаєш мене і я буду казати:
“Wow in  I have a lot of followers there and I
"Вау в мене там купа фоловерів і в мене
will have a great
буде класний
mood and a cool video" Subscribe to my
настро круті видео" Підпишись на мій
Instagram pop Andrey
Instagram попик Андрей
Otak Let me give you a check
Отак Давай я тебе очекаю